A Bundle of Trouble: An Aurora Teagarden Mystery is a mystery,
tv movie, drama film directed by Kevin Fair.
Aurora Teagarden and her boyfriend Martin are thrilled when they get
an unexpected visit from his niece and her new baby.
Their excitement is short lived when his niece
disappears and the baby is left behind.
Once again, Aurora finds herself drawn into a deadly investigation as
she risks it all to help Martin reunite with his family.
Aurora Teagarden, played by Candace Cameron Bure.
Martin Bartell, played by Yannick Bisson.
Aida Teagarden, played by Marilu Henner.
Sally Allison, played by Lexa Doig.
Detective Lynn Leggit-Smith, played by Miranda Frigon.
Detective Arthur Smith, played by Peter Benson.
Aurora Teagarden is a fictional character created by author Charlaine Harris.
She is the protagonist of a series of eleven crime
novels written from 1990 to 2017.
Hallmark Movies & Mysteries began  adapting the novels in 2014 for their original film series The Aurora Teagarden
Mysteries with Candace Cameron Bure in the title role, part of the network’s "Mystery Wheel" umbrella series.
In the first book of the series, twenty-eight-year-old Aurora (Roe) Teagarden is a professional librarian at the Lawrenceton Public Library and belongs to
the Real Murders Club, a group of true crime enthusiasts who gather monthly to study famous crimes from the history of their Georgia town.
The tone is emotional and mind_bending.